lasvegasadvisor.com 2006-10-26

# Las Vegas Advisor - Anthony Curtis - Privacy Policy

| 

Huntington Press is committed to protecting your privacy. The following discloses our information collection and use practices for our Website. 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

## WHAT INFORMATION DOES

HUNTINGTON PRESS, LASVEGASADVISOR.COM AND SHOPLVA.COM (the "SITE") COLLECT AND HOW IS IT USED? When you place an order, download an evaluation, join a discussion list, subscribe to a newsletter, or contact us for support (technical or customer), we ask for your contact or billing information which is used for internal operations and/or to provide you with updated information on our products. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. If you contact us for technical support, we may invite you afterwards to let us know how we're doing by participating in an online survey. Users may opt-out of receiving future marketing mailings; see the opt-out section below. 

## CERTAIN EXCEPTIONAL DISCLOSURES

We may disclose your information if necessary to protect our legal rights or if the information relates to actual or threatened harmful conduct. Disclosure may be required by law or if we receive legal process. 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

## HOW DOES THE SITE USE COOKIES?

We use "cookies" to help create a more effective and convenient site experience. By showing us how and when visitors use the site, "cookies" help us determine which areas are popular and which are not. Many improvements and updates to the site are based on data such as total number of visitors and pages viewed. Huntington Press.com does not store any sensitive information in the cookie. 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

## WHAT MEASURES ARE IN PLACE TO PROTECT CUSTOMER INFORMATION?

Our order process is encrypted using the SSL (Secure Socket Layer) protocol. 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

## HOW DOES HUNTINGTON PRESS

USE MY E-MAIL ADDRESS AND CAN I OPT-OUT OF RECEIVING Huntington Press E-MAIL MESSAGES? Download an evalaution: We ask for your e-mail address before downloading a free product evaluation. If at anytime you decide that you do not want to receive further marketing messages from us, each e-mail will include a link to our unsubscribe page. Your contact information may be forwarded to an authorized Huntington Press reseller in your area, in which case you may need to follow-up with them. Unsubscribing will not interrupt any ongoing conversations you may be having with Huntington Press. Contacting us for technical or customer support: Your e-mail address will be used to respond to your query. In some cases, we may invite you to participate in an online survey to let us know how we are doing. Subscribing to the Las Vegas Advisor Online Newsletter: When you sign up for the Huntington Press Newsletter, your e-mail address is not used for any purpose other than to send you the newsletter on a monthly basis. You may unsubscribe from the newsletter here. Subscribing to a discussion list: When you sign up for a discussion list, your e-mail address is not used for any purpose other than to send you the discussion list in the format you choose on the discussion lists page. You may unsubscribe or change your format preference from the discussion lists page. If you are using the same e-mail address for multiple items above, the e-mail usage information for 'downloading an evaluation' takes precedent over all other e-mail usage information. You may also remove yourself from our marketing list by sending an e-mail to [cs@huntingtonpress.com](mailto:cs@huntingtonpress.com) from the e-mail address you would like to unsubscribe from If you opt out or unsubscribe, we may, in compliance with the United States CAN SPAM Act of 2003, run our suppression list (addresses not to be emailed) against another list of names for an Huntington Press mailing or provide our suppression list to a third party for such verification. When you opt-out or unsubscribe, you are doing so from our marketing messages. Huntington Press may continue to send you transactional messages relevant to our business relationship. Transactional messages include information on product updates and upgrades, Service Agreement and subscription expirations and renewals, responses to inquiries, surveys and other information related to the product you downloaded or purchased. 

## CAN I CHANGE/MODIFY MY CONTACT INFO?

Huntington Press gives users the option to modify their contact information previously provided. Send e-mail to: davidm@HuntingtonPress.com 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

## ADWARE POLICY

Huntington Press does not embed advertising (adware) in any of our software, for two principal reasons. First, adware can be used to monitor your use of software (such as sites selected or files used) or to provide demographic data about you to third parties. Second, we consider it very important not to compromise the quality, speed, and ease of use of our software by displaying ads in it. 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

## OTHER SITES

This site contains links to other sites; Huntington Press is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

## YOUR CONSENT TO THIS POLICY

By using our site, you agree to this Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change it by posting a new version on our site. 

## LEGAL

This site operates as-is and as available. Any warranties of accuracy, quality, title, fitness or merchantability are disclaimed. We are not liable for direct, indirect, incidental or consequential damages, or for events beyond our direct control. By using our site, you agree to this Policy. This is our entire and exclusive Privacy Policy and it supersedes any earlier version. We may change it by posting a new version on our site. Nevada law governs this Policy, excluding conflicts of law principles. Any provision of this Policy that is illegal or unenforceable shall be deemed automatically conformed to the minimum requirements of law. Any legal actions against us must be commenced in Nevada within one year after the claim arose, or be barred. 

\--------------------------------------------------------------------------------

## CONTACTING Huntington Press

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, please contact us:

Huntington Press  
3665 Procyon Ave  
Las Vegas, NV 89103   
702.252.0655
